Stealing Lust is a romance film directed by Hank Hoffman.
For confident millennial Katie, three days of angry, sexy roommates, a
cheating girlfriend and a lemonade stand are no problem at all.
Katie, played by Lena Anderson.
Lust (Arabic: الشوق, translit.
El Shoq) is a 2010 Egyptian drama film directed by Khaled El Hagar.
It stars Ruby, Ahmed Azmi and Sawsan Badr.
Lust was reviewed at the 34th Cairo International Film Festival.
In the Arab world of film production, it is the oldest annual cinema event.
According to Daily News, “Lust” is an interesting and provocative contribution to this year’s festival." The
Executive Producer Producer of Lust was Amr El Safie while Dima Al-Joundi, and Mohamed Yassine produced it.
The film was selected as the Egyptian entry for the Best Foreign Language Film at
the 84th Academy Awards, but it did not make the final shortlist.
Lust was produced and distributed by Arabica Movies
and was released on January 5, 2011.
The tone is emotional.